[
    {
        "front": "しごと",
        "back": "仕事 \njob",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "しかた",
        "back": "仕方 \nway of doing",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "しかたがない",
        "back": "仕方がない \nno choice, no option",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "しごと",
        "back": "仕事 \nwork",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいじ",
        "back": "大事 \nimportant",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "かじ",
        "back": "火事 \nfire incident",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ようじ",
        "back": "用事 \nsomething to do",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ことし",
        "back": "事 \nthing, matter",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぎん",
        "back": "銀 \nsilver",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぎんこう",
        "back": "銀行 \nbank",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぎんざ",
        "back": "銀座 \n(place)",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぎんこういん",
        "back": "銀行員 \nbank employee",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいしゃいん",
        "back": "会社員 \ncompany employee",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "てんいん",
        "back": "店員 \nshopkeeper",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいいん",
        "back": "会員 \nmembership",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "いしゃ",
        "back": "医者 \ndoctor",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "いがく",
        "back": "医学 \nmedical science",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "いいん",
        "back": "医院 \ndoctor's office",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "もの",
        "back": "者 \nperson",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "がくしゃ",
        "back": "学者 \nscholar",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "はいしゃ",
        "back": "歯医者 \ndentist",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "さくしゃ",
        "back": "作者 \nauthor",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "はたらく",
        "back": "働く \nto work",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ろうどうしゃ",
        "back": "労働者 \nlabor work",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "はたらきもの",
        "back": "働き者 \nhard working person",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "なまけもの",
        "back": "怠け者 \nlazy person",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほんや",
        "back": "本屋 \nbook store",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "おくじょう",
        "back": "屋上 \nterrace, root",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "やおや",
        "back": "八百屋 \nvegetable / grocery shop",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "へや",
        "back": "部屋 \nroom",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "うむ",
        "back": "産 \nto give birth",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "せいさん",
        "back": "生産 \nto manufacture",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ざいさん",
        "back": "財産 \nfortune",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "さんぎょう",
        "back": "産業 \nmanufacturing industry",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "じゅうぎょう",
        "back": "従業 \nclass",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうぎょう",
        "back": "工業 \nmanufacture, industry",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほんじつきゅう",
        "back": "本日休 \nclosed today",
        "chapter": "N4 K6"
    }
]